Contact

deeannaopstedahl@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/deeannaopstedahl-4a56b14b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Safety
ACLS

DeeAnna Opstedahl

Vice President of Patient Care Services (CNO) at St. Joseph's Hospital and Health Center

Dickinson, North Dakota

Summary

Experienced Vice President Patient Care Services with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Healthcare Consulting, Medical-Surgical, JCAHO, Emergency Medicine, CNOR, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and many other healthcare associated certifications. Strong healthcare services professional with a MSN focused in Leadership and Management from Walden University. Is on the board of NDNA, member of Sigma Theta Tau and International Nurses, President of NDONE, and state representative of North Dakota for AONE.

Experience

St. Joseph's Hospital and Health Center Vice President of Patient Care Services (CNO) March 2014 - Present (6 years 5 months) Dickinson.ND

St. Joseph Hospital and Health Center Director of Surgery January 2010 - March 2014 (4 years 3 months)

Education

Walden University
MSN, Leadership and Management · (2011 - 2013)

South Dakota State University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing Science (1986 - 2000)